Register of the Victor Gilinsky Papers, 1943-1984
Hoover Institution Archives
- REACTOR SITES, 1974-1984
  - Zimmer (Ohio)
    - 1983 Aug.-Dec. Torrey Pines Technology report, "Independent Review of Zimmer Project Management," 1983 Sept. 2; presentation to the NRC, Sept. 28; Bechtel replaced Henry J. Kaiser Co. as construction company, 1983 Nov.; utility company (CG&E) suggests Ebasco Services Inc. as the independent auditor of CG&E's "Plan to Verify the Quality of Construction (PVQC)"; materials for NRC meeting, including Bechtel Power Corp., "Completion Forecast and Project Schedule", Dec. 15 (Box 481., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 Dec.-1984 Jan. Materials relating to NRC meeting, Dec. 15 (contd.); CG&E's "Plan to Verify the Quality of Construction" and "Continuation of Construction Plan" submitted, Dec. 16; PVQC plan approved, Dec. 29; project scrapped, 97% complete, 1984 Jan. (Box 482., Folder 1-8)
  - Zion (Illinois)
    - General. "Zion Probabilistic Safety Study" (Box 483., Folder 1-4)
    - 1981 Sept.-1983 Aug. Inspection report, 1981 Sept. 2; GAO report on economic impact of closing the plant, 1981 Nov. 4; investigation of drug abuse allegations, 1982 Jan.-July; fire in diesel generator room, 1982 Aug.; enforcement action, 1982 July 2 and report on employee overexposure incident, ca. 1983 Jan.; enforcement actions for security violations, 1983 May 9 and Aug. 26 (SEE ALSO: REACTOR SITES/Zimmer/NRC meeting May 26) (Folder 5-10)
- GENERAL THREE MILE ISLAND INVESTIGATIONS, 1979-1984
  - General
    - General, 1979 June-1981 March. Relates to public reaction, and includes material relating to an advertisement by Edward Teller and Dresser Industries (Box 484., Folder 1)
    - Notes. G.K. Wandling (Babcock and Wilcox employee) (Folder 2-3)
    - Telephone records. Primarily Incident Response Center transcripts
      - General. These annotated transcript sections were separated from the larger body which follows by Dr. Gilinsky's office (to aid in preparing his depositions for the Rogovin Commission, 1979 Aug.?)
        - General. Isolated pages and supplemental material such as chronologies, telephone logs and a notebook (Folder 4-6)
        - Day 1 (Wednesday, March 28, 1979)
          - Channel 2/20 (Folder 7)
          - Channel 6/24 (Folder 8)
          - Channel 7/25 (Folder 9)
        - Day 2 (Thursday, March 29, 1979)
          - Channel 6 (Folder 10)
        - Day 3 (Friday, March 30, 1979)
          - Channel 6/24 (Folder 11)
          - Channel 7/25 (Box 485., Folder 1)
        - Day 4 (Saturday, March 31, 1979)
          - Channel 6/24 (Folder 2)
          - Channel 17/20 (Folder 3)
        - Day 5 (Sunday, April 1, 1979)
          - Channel 2/20 (Folder 4)
          - Channel 12/VIP 1 (Folder 5)
          - Channel 17/20 (Folder 6)
      - Day 1
        - Channel 2/20 (Folder 7-9)
        - Channel 3/21 (Folder 10-11)
        - Channel 4/22 (Box 486., Folder 1)
        - Channel 5/23 (Folder 2-3)
        - Channel 6/24 (Folder 4-5)
        - Channel 7/25 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 8/26 (Box 487., Folder 1)
        - Channel 9/27 (Folder 2)
        - Channel 10/28 (Folder 3)
        - Channel 11/30 (Folder 4)
        - Channel 12/VIP 1 (Folder 5)
        - Channel 13/29 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 16/OUT 2 (Folder 7)
        - Channel 17/203C (Folder 8-9)
        - Channel 19/203D (Folder 10-11)
      - Day 2
        - Channel 2 (Folder 12-13)
        - Channel 2 (contd.) (Box 488., Folder 1-2)
        - Channel 3/21 (Folder 3-6)
        - Channel 4/22 (Folder 7-8)
        - Channel 4/22 (contd.) (Box 489., Folder 1-2)
        - Channel 5/23 (Folder 3-4)
        - Channel 6 (Folder 5-7)
        - Channel 7/25 (Box 490., Folder 1-2)
        - Channel 8/26 (Folder 3)
        - Channel 10 (Folder 4)
        - Channel 11/30 (Folder 5)
        - Channel 12/VIP 1 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 13/29 (Folder 7)
        - Channel 15/OUT 1 (Folder 8)
        - Channel 16/OUT 2 (Folder 9)
        - Channel 17/203C (Folder 10)
        - Channel 17 (contd.) (Box 491., Folder 1)
        - Channel 19/203D (Folder 2-3)
      - Day 3
        - Channel 2/20 (Folder 4-6)
        - Channel 3/21 (Box 492., Folder 1-4)
        - Channel 4/22 (Folder 5)
        - Channel 5/23 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 6/24 (Folder 7)
        - Channel 6/24 (contd.) (Box 493., Folder 1)
        - Channel 7/25 (Folder 2-3)
        - Channel 10/28 (Folder 4-5)
        - Channel 11/30 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 12/VIP 1 (Folder 7-8)
        - Channel 13/29 (Folder 9)
        - Channel 14/VIP 2 (Folder 10)
        - Channel 15/OUT 1 (Box 494., Folder 1)
        - Channel 16/OUT 2 (Folder 2)
        - Channel 17/203C (Folder 3-5)
        - Channel 18/31 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 19/203D (Folder 7-8)
      - Day 4
        - Channel 2/20 (Box 495., Folder 1-2)
        - Channel 3/21 (Folder 3-4)
        - Channel 4/22 (Folder 5)
        - Channel 5/23 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 6/24 (Box 496., Folder 1-3)
        - Channel 7/25 (Folder 4-5)
        - Channel 9/27 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 10/28 (Box 497., Folder 1-4)
        - Channel 11/30 (Folder 5)
        - Channel 12/VIP 1 (Folder 6-7)
        - Channel 13/29 (Box 498., Folder 1)
        - Channel 15/OUT 1 (Folder 2-3)
        - Channel 16/OUT 2 (Folder 4)
        - Channel 17/203C (Folder 5-7)
        - Channel 18/31 (Folder 8)
        - Channel 19/203D (Box 499., Folder 1-2)
      - Day 5
        - Channel 2/20 (Folder 3-5)
        - Channel 3/21 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 3/21 (contd.) (Box 500., Folder 1)
        - Channel 4/22 (Folder 2)
        - Channel 5/23 (Folder 3)
        - Channel 6/24 (Folder 4-6)
        - Channel 7/25 (Box 501., Folder 1)
        - Channel 10/28 (Folder 2-4)
        - Channel 11/30 (Folder 5)
        - Channel 12/VIP 1 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 13/29 (Folder 7)
        - Channel 15/OUT 1 (Box 502., Folder 1)
        - Channel 16/OUT 2 (Folder 2)
        - Channel 17/203C (Folder 3-5)
        - Channel 18/31 (Folder 6)
        - Channel 19/203D (Folder 7-8)
    - Legal materials
      - General Public Utilities (GPU) v. Babcock and Wilcox (B&W)
        - General
          - General. Clippings, 1982 Nov.-Dec. (Box 503., Folder 1)
          - NRC review of transcripts
            - General
              - General. Notebook (Folder 2)
              - 1982 Nov.-1983 Sept. Includes a report by the Office of the General Counsel, 1983 April 14 (Folder 3-7)
          - NRC review of transcripts (Contd.)
            - Report. "GPU v. B&W Lawsuit Review and its Effect on TMI-1," 1983 Sept. Drafts and Final (Vol. 1) (Folder 8-9)
            - Report (contd.) (Vol. 2-Appendices) (Box 504., Folder 1)
        - Transcripts of court proceedings
          - 1982 Nov. 1-2 (Folder 2-4)
          - 1982 Nov. 3-12 (Box 505., Folder 1-7)
          - 1982 Nov. 15-22 (Box 506., Folder 1-6)
          - 1982 Nov. 23-Dec. 7 (Box 507., Folder 1-7)
          - 1982 Dec. 8-17 (Box 508., Folder 1-6)
          - 1982 Dec. 20-1983 Jan. 4 (Box 509., Folder 1-6)
          - 1983 Jan. 5-14 (Box 510., Folder 1-7)
          - 1983 Jan. 18-20 (Box 511., Folder 1-3)
      - GPU v. NRC. Relates to alleged regulatory negligence on the part of the NRC, 1980 Dec.-1981 June (Folder 4)
      - Metropolitan Edison Co. et al. (including the NRC) v. People Against Nuclear Energy (PANE). Printed copies of Supreme Court decisions, 1983 April 19 (Folder 5)
      - PANE v. NRC. Relates to the issue of psychological stress, primarily resulting from the proposed restart of the TMI-1 power station (Folder 6-8)
        - 1982 May-Sept.
      - People of TMI et al. v. Hendrie et al. Relates to the venting of krypton gas during decontamination of the TMI-2 power station, 1982 June-1984 June (Box 512., Folder 1-5)
  - Department of Energy (DOE). Report entitled "Investigation of Hydrogen Burn Damage at the Three Mile Island Unit 2 Reactor Building," 1982 June (Folder 6)
  - Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI)'s Nuclear Safety Analysis Center (NSAC). Reports
    - "Analysis of Three Mile Island Unit 2 Accident," 1979 July-Oct. Includes indexed bibliography
      - Report (Folder 7)
      - Bibliography (Box 513., Folder 1-2)
    - "A Proposed National Nuclear Safety Goal," 1980 March (Folder 3)
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Inc. Serial issue, 1979 Nov. (Folder 4)
  - NRC Special Inquiry Group (Rogovin Commission). This was an independent study commissioned by the NRC and prepared under the direction of the law firm of Rogovin, Stern and Huge
    - General. Relates primarily to NRC review of the report
      - 1979 June-1980 Jan. (Folder 5-9)
      - 1980 Feb.-1983 May (Box 514., Folder 1-3)
    - Deposition by Dr. Gilinsky
      - General. Primarily reference material used in preparing the deposition: letters, memoranda, chronologies, notes, and the deposition of Thomas R. Gibbon (Folder 4-5)
      - Deposition, 1979 Oct. 5 (Folder 6)
    - Report, "Three Mile Island: A Report to the Commissioners and to the Public" (NUREG/CR-1250)
      - General. Presentation to the Commission, 1980 Jan. 24. Transcript (two versions) (Folder 7-8)
      - Draft copy. (Vol. II, parts 1-3 only) (Box 515., Folder 1-6)
      - Final copy. Includes review notes (Box 516., Folder 1-4)
  - Pennsylvania, State of
    - Advisory Panel for Health Research Studies. Transcript, 1982 June 10 (Box 517., Folder 1)
    - Governor's Commission on Three Mile Island. Report and letter from Lt. Gov. William W. Scranton, III, 1980 Feb. (Folder 2)
    - House of Representatives. Report by Democratic members of select committee on Three Mile Island, 1979 Oct. (Folder 3)
    - Public Utilities Commission. Transcript of testimony by William S. Lee (President and CEO of Duke Power Co.) 1980 Jan. 30 (Folder 4)
  - President's Commission on the Accident (Kemeny Commission)
    - General
      - 1979 April-June. Primarily NRC analysis of hearings. Includes executive order, 1979 April 11 (Folder 5-8)
      - 1979 June-Nov. Includes request by the White House (Frank Press) for an NRC analysis of the Kemeny Commission recommendations (Box 518., Folder 1-8)
      - 1979 Nov.-Dec. Includes President Carter's responses to the Kemeny Commission report (Box 519., Folder 1-2)
    - Depositions and testimony
      - Ahearne, John F. (NRC Commissioner), Aug. 29
        - Annotated copy with synopsis (Folder 3)
        - Corrected copy (Folder 4)
      - Arnold, R.C. (V.P.-Generation, GPU), May 30 (Folder 5)
      - Bradford, Peter A. (NRC Commissioner), Sept. 10 (Folder 6-7)
      - Crietz, Walter M. (Pres., Met. Edison), May 18 (Box 520., Folder 1)
      - Dieckamp, Herman (Pres., GPU), May 18 (Folder 2)
      - Gilinsky, Victor (NRC Commissioner)
        - June 1. Testimony transcript (Folder 3)
        - Sept. 8
          - General. Background material (Folder 4)
          - Deposition (Folder 5)
      - Gossick, Lee V. (NRC Exec. Dir. for Operations), 1979 Aug. 9 (Folder 6)
      - Hendrie, Joseph M. (NRC Chairman), Sept. 7 (Folder 7-8)
      - Herbein, John C. (V.P.-Generation, Met. Edison), May 18 (Folder 9)
      - Kennedy, Richard T. (NRC Commissioner), Sept. 5 (Box 521., Folder 1)
      - Miller, Gary P. (TMI Station Manager), May 18 (Folder 2)
    - Reports
      - General (Folder 3)
        - Report of the President's Commission on the Accident at Three Mile Island, The Need for Change: The Legacy of TMI
        - "Supplemental Views by Members of the President's Commission on the Accident at Three Mile Island," 1979 Oct.
      - Office of Chief Counsel
        - "The Nuclear Regulatory Commission" (Folder 4)
        - "The Role of the Managing Utility and its Suppliers" (Folder 5)
      - Technical Assessment Task Force, Vol. I (Folder 6)
        - "Technical Staff Analysis Reports Summary"
        - "Summary Sequence of Events"
      - Technical Assessment Task Force, Vol. II (Folder 7)
        - "Chemistry"
        - "Thermal Hydraulics"
        - "Core Damage"
        - "WASH 1400-Reactor Safety Study"
        - "Alternative Event Sequences"
      - Technical Assessment Task Force, Vol. III (Box 522., Folder 1)
        - "Selection, Training, Qualification, and Licensing of Three Mile Island Reactor Operating Personnel"
        - "Technical Assessment of Operating, Abnormal, and Emergency Procedures"
        - "Control Room Design and Performance"
      - Technical Assessment Task Force, Vol. IV
        - "Quality Assurance" (Folder 2)
        - "Condensate Polishing System" (Folder 3)
        - "Closed Emergency Feedwater Valves"
        - "Pilot-Operated Relief Valve Design and Performance"
        - "Containment: Transport of Radioactivity from the TMI-2 Core to the Environs"
        - "Iodine Filter Performance" (Folder 4)
      - Public Health and Safety Task Force
        - "Public Health and Safety Summary" (Folder 5)
        - "Health Physics and Dosimetry"
        - "Radiation Health Effects" (Folder 6)
        - "Behavioral Effects Task Force Report"
        - "Public Health and Epidemiology" (Folder 7)
      - Emergency Preparedness and Response Task Force "Emergency Preparedness" "Emergency Response" (Folder 8)
      - Public's Right to Information Task Force. "Report of the Public's Right to Information Task Force" (Box 523., Folder 1)
    - Transcripts of meetings
      - General. Press conference, 1979 May 31 (Folder 2-4)
      - April 25-27 (Folder 5-8)
      - May 17 (Box 524., Folder 1)
      - May 19 (Folder 2-3)
      - May 30-31 (Folder 4-7)
      - June 1 (Box 525., Folder 1)
      - July 18 (Folder 2-3)
      - Aug. 2 (Folder 4)
      - Aug. 21-22 (Folder 5-6)
      - Aug. 23 (Box 526., Folder 1-2)
      - Sept. 15 (Folder 3-4)
      - Sept. 29 (Folder 5-6)
      - Sept. 30 (Box 527., Folder 1-2)
      - Oct. 1-2 (Folder 3-6)
      - Oct. 15 (Folder 7)
      - Oct. 16 (Box 528., Folder 1-2)
      - Oct. 20-21 (Folder 3-7)
      - Oct. 22 (Box 529., Folder 1)
  - U.S. Congress
    - General
      - General. Correspondence, with Congressional Record excerpts and statements, 1979 March 28-1980 Feb. 15 (Folder 2-5)
      - Joint House-Senate hearings. Transcript and memorandum, 1979 Nov. 1 (Folder 6)
    - House of Representatives
      - Dingell Committee. Transcript, 1979 Nov. 5 (Folder 7)
      - McCormack Committee. Hearing transcript, 1979 Nov. 14; report, 1980 March (Folder 8-9)
      - Moffett Committee. Hearing transcript, 1980 Feb. 23 (Box 530., Folder 1)
      - Udall Committee. Hearings, 1979 March 29, May 21, 1980 May, 1983 April 26 (Folder 2-5)
    - Senate
      - Glenn/Percy Committee, 1979 April-May. Hearing, May 9 (Folder 6-7)
      - Hart/Simpson Committee
        - 1979 April 10. Includes transcript (Folder 8-9)
        - 1979 April-1980 Sept. Hearings, 1979 April 23, April 30, Oct. 2-3, Nov. 8; report, 1980 July (Box 531., Folder 1-7)
      - Public Works Committee (Sen. Jennings Randolph, Chairman). Gilinsky testimony, June 14 (Folder 8)
- NRC THREE MILE ISLAND INVESTIGATIONS, 1973-1984
  - General
    - General
      - General. Primarily pre-event materials
        - General, 1976-1977. Includes a supplement to the Environmental Impact Statement (Box 532., Folder 1)
        - Notebook, 1978 Feb.-1979 March (Folder 2-4)
        - Reports. Primarily Licensee Event Reports, with correspondence, 1973 July-1979 Feb. (Folder 5-8)
      - 1979 March-May 17 (Box 533., Folder 1-9)
      - 1979 May 18-July 3 (Box 534., Folder 1-9)
      - 1979 July 5-Sept. 14. Includes order modifying license, Sept. 14 (Box 535., Folder 1-9)
      - 1979 Sept. 17-1980 March 20 (Box 536., Folder 1-10)
      - 1980 March 21-1981 July 27 (Box 537., Folder 1-10)
      - 1981 Aug.-Sept. (Box 538., Folder 1)
    - Meeting transcripts
      - General, 1979 April-1981 March. Includes chronologies, memoranda, and transcript fragments (Folder 2)
      - Closed meetings
        - 1979 March 30-April 5. Joint meeting with ACRS, April 5 (Folder 3-8)
        - 1979 April 5 (contd.)-April 10 (Box 539., Folder 1-6)
        - 1979 April 13-Oct. 22 (Box 540., Folder 1-10)
        - 1979 Oct. 23-1982 Dec. 1. NOTE: Beginning in 1981 Oct., the transcripts are those released to the Philadelphia Inquirer (Box 541., Folder 1-13)
        - 1982 Dec. 6-1983 Nov. 8 (Box 542., Folder 1-14)
        - 1984 Jan. 10-Jan. 26 (Box 543., Folder 1-4)
      - Open meetings
        - 1979 March 29-April 25 (Folder 5-12)
        - 1979 April 25-1980 March 19 (Box 544., Folder 1-6)
    - Preliminary Notification event reports (Folder 7-9)
    - Press materials
      - General, 1979 March 28-1980 March 29. Articles, interviews, wire reports, clippings (Box 545., Folder 1-6)
      - NRC press conferences, 1979 April 2-May 7 (Folder 7-8)
    - Reports
      - 1979 April. "Evaluation of Long-term Post Accident Core Cooling of TMI Unit 2" (NUREG 0557) (Box 546., Folder 1)
      - 1979 Dec. "Report to the NRC from the Staff Panel on the Commission's Determination of an Extraordinary Nuclear Occurence (ENO)" (NUREG 0637) (Folder 2)
      - 1980 Dec. "Control Room Design Review Report for TMI-1" (NUREG 0752) Includes Supplement #1. (Folder 3)
  - Accident sequence. Chronologies, 1979 March 30-1980 Jan. 14 (Folder 4-8)
  - Advisory Committee on Reactor Safeguards
    - General. Includes letter and report to the Rogovin Commission relating to ACRS recommendations, 1979 July 25
      - 1979 April 7-1980 Dec. 10 (Box 547., Folder 1-8)
      - 1981 Feb. 10-Sept. 23 (Box 548., Folder 1-2)
    - Meeting transcripts
      - General, 1979 April 5-17. Primarily joint meetings with the NRC (Folder 3-5)
      - General meetings, 1979
        - April 5 (Meeting #228) (Folder 6)
        - April 6 (#228 contd.) (Box 549., Folder 1)
        - May 10-11 (#229) (Folder 2-3)
        - May 12 (#229 contd.) (Box 550., Folder 1)
        - June 14-15 (#230) (Folder 2-3)
      - TMI Subcommittee (Box 551., Folder 1-4)
        - 1979 April 4-May 9
        - 1979 May 31-June 6 (Box 552., Folder 1-3)
        - 1979 June 7-July 11 (Box 553., Folder 1-3)
        - 1979 July 26-Aug. 8 (Box 554., Folder 1-3)
        - 1981 June 25 (Folder 4)
  - Babcock and Wilcox. Primarily post-TMI re-evaluation of generic design and sister plants
    - General. Other reactors
      - General
        - 1979 April-May (Folder 5-7)
        - 1979 June-1980 May (Box 555., Folder 1)
      - Arkansas Unit 1, 1979 April-Aug. (Folder 2)
      - Davis Besse, 1979 April-Aug. NOTE: A very similar accident occured here 1977 Sept. 24, yet was recognized and controlled (Folder 3-4)
      - Oconee, 1979 April-Aug. (Folder 5)
      - Rancho Seco
        - General
          - 1978 March-June (Folder 6-7)
          - 1979 June-1980 March (Box 556., Folder 1-2)
        - Brown, Gov. Edmund, Jr. Correspondence with the NRC, 1979 April 1-5 (Folder 3)
    - 1978 Jan. C. Michelson, "Decay Heat Removal during a Very Small Break LOCA for a B&W 205-Fuel-Assembly PWR" (Folder 4)
    - 1979 May. NRC Office of Inspector and Auditor, "Michelson Report Events and Levels of Review". Includes memoranda and notes, 1979 May-Sept. (Folder 5-7)
    - 1979 May. "Staff Report on the Generic Assessment of Feedwater Transients in Pressurized Water Reactors Designed by the B&W Company" (NUREG 0560) (Folder 8)
    - 1979 Sept. NRC Office of Inspection and Enforcement, "Report of Investigation. Babcock and Wilcox, Possible Violation of 10CFR Part 21" (Folder 9)
    - 1979 Oct. NRC Office of Nuclear Reactor Regulation, "Interim Report on Sensitivity Studies of the B&W Reactor Design". Includes a memorandum describing the choice of the Crystal River facility as the focus of study (Folder 10)
    - 1980 Jan. NRC Office of Inspection and Enforcement, "Report of Investigation". Relates to the failure of Babcock and Wilcox to report staff concerns prior to TMI regarding system response to transients (Box 557., Folder 1)
    - 1980 March "Transient Response of Babcock and Wilcox Reactors" (NUREG 0667). Draft of the report of the NRR B&W Reactor Transient Response Task Force (Folder 2)
  - Corrective efforts. SEE ALSO: DOMESTIC NUCLEAR REACTOR LICENSING AND REGULATION/Regulatory Reform
    - General
      - Citizens Advisory Board, 1979 Nov.-1980 May (Folder 3)
      - Safety Board (proposed), 1979 May-July Action Plan/Lessons Learned (Folder 4)
      - General
        - 1979 May-1980 Jan. (Folder 5-8)
        - 1980 Feb.-1981 Oct. (Box 558., Folder 1-6)
      - Reports
        - 1979 July. "TMI Lessons Learned Task Force Status Report and Short-Term Recommendations" (NUREG 0578) (Folder 7)
        - 1979 Oct. "TMI-2 Lessons Learned Task Force Final Report" (NUREG 0585) (Box 559., Folder 1)
        - 1979 Oct. "Report to the Director, Office of Inspection and Enforcement on Lessons Learned from TMI" (NUREG 0616) (Folder 2)
        - 1979 Oct. "Draft Action Plans for Implementing Recommendations of the President's Commission and Other Studies of the TMI-2 Accident" (Folder 3-5)
        - 1980 May. "NRC Action Plans Developed as a Result of the TMI-2 Accident" (Folder 6-8)
        - 1980 Nov. "Clarification of the TMI Action Plan Requirements". Includes a supplement, 1983 Jan. (Box 560., Folder 1)
        - 1981 June. "NRC's Implementation of the TMI Action Plan" (Folder 2)
  - Decontamination and clean-up of the TMI-2 reactor
    - General. Collected materials (notebooks?) relating primarily to the proposed venting of krypton-85
      - 1980 Feb.-May (Folder 3-8)
      - 1980 Nov. Public meeting, Nov. 10 (Box 561., Folder 1-2)
    - 1979 May-Oct. Relates to the proposed use of an EPICOR-2 clean-up system, the shipment of waste material, environmental assessment, and a lawsuit filed by the city of Lancaster, Pennsylvania (Folder 3-8)
    - 1979 Oct.-1980 March. Continuing assessment of waste disposal (Box 562., Folder 1-9)
    - 1980 April-May. Predominantly relates to the removal of krypton-85 gas, including two reports by Gerald Pollack, March 24 and 31; Udall hearings, May 22 (Box 563., Folder 1-9)
    - 1980 June-Nov. Assessment of financial implications of clean-up, including NRC report entitled, "Potential Impact of Licensee Default on Clean-up of TMI-2" (NUREG 0689), 1980 Nov. (Box 564., Folder 1-10)
    - 1980 Nov.-1981 March. Includes NRC report, "Final Programmatic Environmental Impact Statement Related to Decontamination and Disposal of Radioactive Wastes Resulting from the March 28, 1979 Accident at Three Mile Island Nuclear Station Unit 2", 1981 March (Vol. 1-Report) (Box 565., Folder 1-7)
    - 1981 March-Sept. NRC report, "Final Programmatic Environmental Impact Statement Related to Decontamination and Disposal of Radioactive Wastes Resulting from the March 28, 1979 Accident at Three Mile Island Nuclear Station Unit 2" (Vol. 2-Appendix); continuing assessment of financial issues (Box 566., Folder 1-7)
    - 1981 Oct.-1982 Nov. Hart/Simpson Committee hearings, 1981 Oct. 20; continuing assessment of financial issues; Udall Committee hearings, 1982 April 23 and 27 (Box 567., Folder 1-9)
    - 1983 June-Sept. Material on allegations made by Richard Parks, including an NRC report, 1983 Sept. 7-8; also includes some material on allegations made by Harold W. Hartman, Jr. (SEE: General Public Utilities/TMI-1 restart/Hartman allegations) (Box 568., Folder 1-8)
    - 1983 Dec.-1984 May. Includes NRC reports on clean-up activities and Safety Advisory Board Third Annual Report (Box 569., Folder 1-8)
  - Economic effects, 1980 Feb.-1982 March. Includes materials relating to several proposed bills (S. 1606, H.R. 5963, H.R. 2512) and reports by Arthur Young and Co., "Report on the Analysis and Potential Effects of Bankruptcy," and "Analysis of Strategic Options to Finance Continuing Electric Power Service in the Jersey Central Power & Light Company Franchise Area" (Box 570., Folder 1-8)
  - Emergency response procedures, 1979 March-1983 April. Primarily evacuation plans at the time of the accident (Box 571., Folder 1-2)